Guide to the William Benton Papers 1839-1973
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Speech Files
  Russia, television, "How Should the United States Compete with Russia?," no text, 2/1/57; #11
  Russia, television, "Soviet versus U. S. Education," 6/16/65; #2072
  Russia, television, "Big Red Schoolhouse," 3/1/59; #1250
  Russia, television, "Scientific Rivalry; United States versus U.S.S.R.," no text, 11/3/57; #12
  Russia, television, "Soviet and American Education," no text, 11/18/57; #134
  Russia, television, "Are the Russians Out-Reading Us?," no text, 3/18/58; #276
  Russia, television, "Soviet Challenge; Education," 6/22/56; #2
  Russia, television, "Soviet Challenge; Education," 12/25/57; #121
  Russia, television, "Soviet Challenge; Education," 7/1/58; #801
  Russia, television, "Soviet Union Training Two Million Youngsters as Semi-Professional Craftsmen," 1/12/58; #32
  Russia, television, "U. S. versus Soviet Education," 3/21/66; #2111
  Russia, television, "Education in the Soviet Union," no text, 1/12/58; #27
  Russia, television, "Philosophy of Communism," no text, 11/58; #1112
  Russia, television, Benton's arrival from Crimean Conference, 6/61; #1812
  Russia, testimony, "Soviet Challenge; Science and Technology," 1/28/58; #153
  Russia, testimony, "Soviet Challenge; Science and Technology," 5/1/56; #42
  Russian trip 1955, announcement of Benton's planned trip to Russia and the satellites, 7/22/55; #164
  Russian trip 1955, article, Helen Benton, "Experiences Behind the Iron Curtain," Connecticut College Alumnae News, 3/56; #1003
  Russian trip 1955, article, Helen Benton, series in Connecticut newspapers, 1/56; #773
  Russian trip 1955, article, John Benton, "I Went to School in Moscow," Life, 12/5/55; #191
  Russian trip 1955, article, John Benton, "John Benton's Travelogue; Sweden, Finland, U.S.S.R.," Capital Times, 9/13/60; #1797
  Russian trip 1955, article, John Benton, several newspaper articles, 1955; #252
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, series of Connecticut newspaper articles, 3/56; #106
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, Encyclopaedia Britannica News, 1/56; #105
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, "We're Fooling Ourselves About Russia," American Engineer, 1/57; #7
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, "Trip Behind the Iron Curtain," Herald Tribune, 12/18-21/55; #878
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, "How Strong Is Russia-and How Weak?," New York Times, 6/10/56; #38
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, "Russian Artist's Training," ibid., 12/4/55; #383
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, "What Soviet Artists May Paint," ibid., 12/18/55; #1784
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, "Russia Revisited," North American Newspaper Alliance, 10/60; #1768
  Russian trip 1955, article, William Benton, "Satellite Culture and Mr. Marx," Theatre Arts Magazine, 11/56; #133
  Russian trip 1955, article, Lawrence M. Gould, "Education and Survival," Carleton College Bulletin, 8/58; #1051
  Russian trip 1955, article, Harrison Salisbury, 6/15/58; #282A
  Russian trip 1955, article, Harrison Salisbury, "To Counter Russian Propaganda," New York Times Magazine, 2/9/58; #168
  Russian trip 1955, article, Dorothy Thompson, "Challenge of Soviet Education," Ladies Home Journal, 5/56; #148
  Russian trip 1955, Democratic National Committee campaign publicity tips for 1958, sample release mentions Benton's trip; #1114
  Russian trip 1955, editorial, "Benton Report Bares Soviet Press System," Editor and Publisher, 12/17/55; #1221
  Russian trip 1955, interview, "Russian Trip and Television in the Soviet Orbit," Billboard, 12/15/55; #716
  Russian trip 1955, memo, Helen Benton, 10-11/55; #772
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Budapest, U. S. Minister and other diplomats, (#8), 11/15-18/55; #334
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Budapest, film, (#9), 11/17/55; #335
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Budapest, education, (#10), 11/16/55; #336
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Budapest, theater, (#11), 11/17/55; #337
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Crimean Conference, 5/61; #1807
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, meeting with Mayor, (#14), 11/1/55; #340
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, miscellaneous topics, (#15), 11/55; #341
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, languages, (#16), 11/55; #342
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, visit to collective farm, (#20), 11/55; #346
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, higher education, (#23), 11/55; #349
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, polytechnical education, (#24), 11/2/55; #350
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, film, radio, and television, (#31), 11/1/55; #357
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, motion pictures, (#34), 11/15/55; #360
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, art and art schools, (#36), 10/12-28/55; #362
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, visit to Leningrad Library, (#44), 10/27/55; #366
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, Soviet art, (#35), 11/55; #361A
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, Moscow, education, (#21), 11/8-10/55; #347
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, U. S. Minister about Soviet propaganda and foreign relations, (#12), 11/55; #338
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, annual Kremlin reception for diplomatic corps, (#13), 11/7/55; #339
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, Swiss legation, (#17), 11/55; #343
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, party by Ethiopian ambassador, (#18-#19), 11/3/55; #344-#345
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, University of Moscow, (#22), 11/55; #348
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, education in grade schools, (#25), 11/55; #351
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, history textbooks in Russia, (#26), 11/55; #352
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, advertising in the Soviet Union, (#27), 11/55; #353
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, conversations with Pravda editors, (#28), 11/55; #354
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, conversations with Izvestia editors, (#29), 11/55; #355
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, conversations with Tass officials, (#30), 11/55; #356
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, radio and television, (#32), 11/10-11/55; #358
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, television and films, (#33), 11/10-11/55; #359
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, Deputy Minister of Culture, (#42), 11/55; #361B
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, influence of Stalin and Lenin on Soviet art, (#37), 11/55; #363A
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, Soviet culture, (#38), 11/11/55; #363B
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, The Great Soviet Encyclopedia, (#43), 11/55; #364
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, Directress of Bolshoi Ballet School, (#39), 11/55; #365A
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, Russian ballet, (#40), 11/13/55; #365B
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Kiev, cathedrals and churches, (#41), 11/55; #367
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Prague, (#1), 11/18-19/55; #327
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Prague, (#2), 11/19/55; #328
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Prague, (#3), Minister of Culture, 11/19/55; #329
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Prague, Chief of Book Publishing in Ministry of Culture, (#4), 11/19/55; #330
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Warsaw, miscellaneous topics, (#5), 11/14/55; #331
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Warsaw, miscellaneous topics, (#6), 11/13-14/55; #332
  Russian trip 1955, memo, William Benton, Warsaw, dinner at U. S. Embassy, (#7), 11/55; #333
  Russian trip 1955, photo, Helen Benton, 12/55; #1523
  Russian trip 1955, photo, John Benton, 11/55; #1571
  Russian trip 1955, photo, miscellaneous scenic shots taken by John Benton, 11/55; #1590
  Russian trip 1955, photo, Bentons in Budapest, 11/55; #1579
  Russian trip 1955, photo, John Benton in Russian school, 11/55; #613
  Russian trip 1955, photo, Bentons in Moscow, 11/55; #1153
  Russian trip 1955, photo, negatives, 11/55; #1581
  Russian trip 1955, photo, Bolshoi Ballet taken by John Benton, 11/55; #1580
  Russian trip 1955, photo, miscellaneous; #2049
  Russian trip 1955, photo, Institute for the Study of the U.S.S.R., 4/28/56; #1460
  Russian trip 1955, radio, Helen and John Benton, 11/21/55; #723
  Russian trip 1955, radio, John Benton, Moscow school days, 1/17/56; #1271
  Russian trip 1955, radio, John Benton, Moscow school days, 11/23/55; #18
  Russian trip 1955, article, Benton, forthcoming trip and Encyclopaedia Britannica, 10/11/55; #980
  Russian trip 1955, article, Benton, trip plans, 9/29/55; #1272
  Russian trip 1955, article, Benton, 11/22-23/55; #178
  Russian trip 1955, article, Benton, Radio-Moscow, 11/16/55; #981
  Russian trip 1955, Gurewitsch Report, "Organization of Medicine in the Soviet Union," 1/7/58; #303
  Russian trip 1955, speech, William Benton, "U.S.S.R.; Some Elements of Strength and Some of Weakness," Institute for the Study of the U.S.S.R., 4/28/56; #70
  Russian trip 1955, speech, "Soviet Progress in Education," Council on Foreign Relations, 4/26/56; #71
  Russian trip 1955, speech, "Introducing Yuri Zhukov," 2/19/69; #2219
  Russian trip 1955, speech, "Introducing Yuri Zhukov," trip plans, 11/22/55; #1355
  Russian trip 1955, speech, "Introducing Yuri Zhukov," upcoming trip, 9/15/55; #190
  Russian trip 1962, article, Helen Benton, "Russians Never Had It So Good, But Still Under-privileged," Bridgeport Sunday Herald, 7/29/62; #1309
  Russian trip 1962, article, Helen Benton, "The Evolution of a Soviet Playwright," Saturday Review, 10/27/62; #1309A
  Russian trip 1962, article, John Benton, "Tour of Moscow and Tashkent and Visit to a Collective Farm," North American Newspaper Alliance, 10/7/62; #1903
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "Education in the U.S.S.R.; Cultural Exchange with the U.S.S.R.," Christian Science Monitor, 3/9/62, 3/11/62, 3/20/62; #1327
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "Soviet and American Movies; Can They Co-Exist?," 1963; #1336
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "United States and Soviet Trade Action," Christian Science Monitor, 8/25/62; #1313
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "Big Red Threat; Education," New York World Telegram and Sun, 9/10-13/62; #1311
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "Art for Nikita's Sake," North American Newspaper Alliance, 6/63; #1328
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "Crimean Conference," ibid., 6/61; #1810
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "Educational TV; A New Soviet Challenge," 1963; #1337
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "Inside the Siberian Science City," Saturday Evening Post, 12/22-29/62; #1904
  Russian trip 1962, article, William Benton, "Should We Continue the Cultural Exchange with the U.S.S.R.?," Saturday Review, 10/27/62; #1312
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Chairman of State Committee of Radio and Television, 6/25/62; #1870
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Minister of Public Education, 6/25/62; #1872
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, cultural exchanges, 6/25/62; #1871
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, motion pictures, 6/30/62; #1873
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Moscow University, 6/25/62; #1874
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Mme. Khrushcheva, 7/6/62; #1876
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Deputy Premier, 7/6/62; #1877
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Sovietskaya Hotel, 6/23/62; #1879
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Chief Secretary of U.S.S.R. Academy of Science, 6/25/62; #1880
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Mme. Popova, 6/23/62; #1881
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, cultural exchanges, 6/27/62; #1882
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Simonov and son, 6/23/62; #1883
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Minister of Higher Education, 6/25/62; #1884
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, visit to art studios, 6/27/62; #1885
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, tour, 6/25/62; #1886
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Bolshoi Ballet, 6/62; #1887
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, President of Academy of Pedagogical Sciences, 6/29/62; #1888
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, editor of Ogonek, 6/28/62; #1889
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, notes, Khrushchev book, On the Communist Programme, 7/1/62; #1899
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, staff of Great Soviet Encyclopedia, 6/26/62; #1900
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, U. S.-Soviet relations, 6/27/62; #1901
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Director of U.S.S.R. Radio and Television, 6/28/62; #1902
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Novosibirsk, city square, 7/5/62; #1878
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Novosibirsk, miscellaneous topics, 7/4-5/62; #1892
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Samarkand, furs, 7/3/62; #1890
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Tashkent, officials from Institute of Transportation, 7/2/62; #1893-#1894
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Tashkent, tour of city, 7/2/62; #1895
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Tashkent, Minister of Culture for Uzbekishan, 7/3/62; #1896
  Russian trip 1962, memo, William Benton, Tashkent, Minister of Education for Uzbekishan, 7/3/62; #1897
  Russian trip 1962, memo, photos, 6-7/62; #1317
  Russian trip 1962, memo, radio, 7/22/62; #1305
  Russian trip 1964, article, Alexei Adzhubei, "America from Far and Near," Great Ideas Today, 1964; #1994
  Russian trip 1964, article, Alexei Adzhubei, "Soviet Art; How Real Is Soviet Realism?," 8/64; #1991
  Russian trip 1964, article, Alexei Adzhubei, "Education in the U.S.S.R.," 8/64; #1999
  Russian trip 1964, article, Alexei Adzhubei, "Soviet Artists Branch Out," Christian Science Monitor, 1/7/65; #1991
  Russian trip 1964, article, Alexei Adzhubei, "The Teachers and the Taught in the U.S.S.R.," Britannica Book of the Year, 1965; #2000
  Russian trip 1964, article, Alexei Adzhubei, "Comments on Adzhubei Article," Great Ideas Today, 1964; #1994
  Russian trip 1964, article, Alexei Adzhubei, "What Worries the Men in the Kremlin," Look, 4/20/65; #1993
  Russian trip 1964, article, Alexei Adzhubei, four-article series, North American Newspaper Alliance, 8/64; #1992
  Russian trip 1964, The Teachers and the Taught in the U.S.S.R., 3/66; #2080
  Russian trip 1964, This Is the Challenge; #282
  Russian trip 1964, Harry W. Nerhood, To Russia and Return, 1968; #2238
  Russian trip 1964, George Alexander Lensen, Russia's Eastward Expansion, 1964; #1892A
  Russian trip 1964, interview, "Benton's Russian Visit," Izvestia, 5/64; #1959
  Russian trip 1964, memo, Charles Benton, 9/64; #2042
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Soviet-American relations, 5/18/64; #1961
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, cultural exchange, 5/20/64; #1963
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Khrushchev, 5/28/64; #1960
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, miscellaneous topics, 5/29/64; 1962
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, British Ambassador, 6/2/64; #1971
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, miscellaneous topics, 6/4/64; #1964
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, visit with head of State Committee on Publishing, 6/4/64; #1965
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, visit with head of State Committee on Publishing, medal-giving ceremony, 6/4/64; #1965A
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, editorial staff of Soviet Encyclopedia, 6/5/64; #1966
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Institute of Soviet-American Relations, 6/5/64; #1976
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Simonov, 6/5/64; #1977
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, miscellaneous topics, 6/5/64; #1967
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Communism, leadership in Russia, and Soviet goals, 6/5/64; #1968
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, senior editor of Pravda, 6/5/64; #1969
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Allen Dulles's comments on Benton's 1955 memo, 6/5/64; #1982
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Minister of Higher Education, 6/5/64; #1981
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, television appearance, 6/5/64; #1980
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, the Mamedovs, 6/5/64; #1979
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, U. S. Ambassador, 6/5/64; #1970
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, visit to dacha, 6/9/64; #1974
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, directors of Institute of Soviet-American Relations, 6/8/64; #1978
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Minister of Culture, 6/8/64; #1972
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, miscellaneous topics, 6/10/64; #1973
  Russian trip 1964, memo, William Benton, Moscow, Vice President of State Committee for Cinematography, 6/10/64; #1975
  Russian trip 1964, memo, Milan Herzog, 9/64; #2043
  Russian trip 1964, photo, Russian intellectuals visit Benton home, 11/26/64; #2052A
  Russian trip 1964, radio, 6/25-26/64; #1984
  Russian trip 1964, Soviet television, 5/28/64; #1954
  Sahl, Mort, and James Thurber, "State of Nation's Humor," New York Times, 12/7/58; #1101
  Sandburg, Carl, book, Herbert Mitgang, Letters of Carl Sandburg, 1968; #2222
  Sandburg, photo, 1942; #1418
  Sandburg, photo, autographed; #1403
  Sandburg, record, 1942; #1259
  Schlesinger, Arthur M., A Thousand Days, 1965; #2099
  Schlesinger, "Death Wish of the Democrats," The New Republic, 9/15/58; #905
  Schriftgiesser, Karl, Business and Public Policy, 1967; #2178
  Schriftgiesser, Committee for Economic Development, Business Comes of Age, 1/60; #1374
  Senate, amendment, Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 8/1/51; #642B
  Senate, appointment, to Banking and Currency Committee, 4/3/51; #443
  Senate, appointment, to Joint Committee on Library of Congress, 1/17/51; #577
  Senate, appointment, as Senator, 12/17/49; #1425
  Senate, appointment, to Small Business Committee, 12/5/50; #1176
  Senate, appointment, Charles M. Gallagher, to Benton's Senatorial staff, 4/23/58; #380
  Senate, article, Edward B. Lockett, "What Makes a Good Senator," Coronet, 10/52; #212
  Senate, certificate, Senate election, 11/7/50; #1424
  Senate, election law guide book, 1952; #1028
  Senate, government reorganization, Ernest K. Lindley, "Frank Words on Economy," Newsweek, 3/3/52; #661
  Senate, government reorganization, summary of efforts on behalf of; #314
  Senate, government reorganization, Leadership Award of Citizens Committee for the Hoover Report, 6/20/52; #1468
  Senate, hearings, Appropriations Committee, Appropriations Bill for 1947, 5-6/46; #690B
  Senate, hearings, Atomic Energy Committee, shortage of scientific and engineering power, 4-5/56; #110
  Senate, hearings, Foreign Relations Committee, U. S. Information Program-Resolution #74, part I, 11/52; #208A
  Senate, hearings, Foreign Relations Committee, U. S. Information Program-Resolution #74, part II, 3/53 and 5/53; #208B
  Senate, hearings, Foreign Relations Committee, review of foreign policy, part I, 2-3/58; #60
  Senate, hearings, Government Operations Committee, government security, 3/55; #986
  Senate, hearings, Government Operations Committee, National Defense Education Act, 6/58; #1377. See also National Defense Education Act.
  Senate, hearings, Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, use of television frequencies for educational purposes-Resolution #127, 5/31/51; #689A
  Senate, hearings, Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, establishment of Citizen's Advisory Board on radio and television, volume I, 9/51; #506
  Senate, hearings, Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, establishment of Citizen's Advisory Board on radio and television, volume II, 9/51; #506A
  Senate, hearings, Judiciary Committee, nomination of President and Vice President, 3-4/55; #1098
  Senate, hearings, Labor and Public Welfare Committee, establishment of Commission on Ethics in Government-Resolution #21, 6-7/51; #483
  Senate, hearings, Labor and Public Welfare Committee, limitation on debate in Senate, amendment of Rule XXII, 10/2-23/51; #1111
  Senate, Benton interview, Russian press in the United States, 8/13/50; #1865
  Senate, letter, Benton to Connecticut constituents, Universal Military Training Act, 3/28/51; #798
  Senate, letter, Walter E. Cosgriff to Benton, support via campaign contribution for government reorganization, 7/3/52; #1034
  Senate, letter, Justice Department to Benton, ownership of land under island waters and the marginal sea, 8/9/51; #822
  Senate, letter, Jack McFall to Benton, Archbishop Grosz of Hungary, 7/5/51; #976
  Senate, letter, James W. Murphy to Benton, 7/19/51; #1543
  Senate, letter, S. Abbot Smith to Benton on problems of small business, 8/8/50; #698
  Senate, letter, State Department to Benton, Bishop Padewski and Polish National Catholic Church, 1/25/51; #874
  Senate, Marshall Plan of Ideas. See Marshall Plan of Ideas.
  Senate, photo, Boys Nation, 1950; #1577
  Senate, photo, Congressional luncheon, 1950; #1573
  Senate, photo, 1950; #1576
  Senate, photo, Barkley greets new Senators, 1/3/50; #1531
  Senate, photo, Girls Nation, 1951; #1572
  Senate, photo, miscellaneous for Senate years, 1950-1952; #1443
  Senate, photo, Congressional radio room, 5/52; #1480
  Senate, press conference, "Benton Amendment to the Mutual Security Act," 11/16/51; #452
  Senate, radio, "Foreign Policy," 1950; #583
  Senate, radio, "Domestic Policy," 10/24/50; #628
  Senate, radio, "Immigration Laws and Connecticut Responsibility," 1950; #916
  Senate, radio, "Congress's Record; Current Session"; #921
  Senate, radio, "Legislative Accomplishments of Second Session of 81st Congress," 1950; #922
  Senate, radio, "Immigration Legislation," 3/8/50; #964
  Senate, radio, "Letters from Constituents," 3/9/50; #920
  Senate, radio, "Current Issues in Washington," 3/26/50; #1121
  Senate, radio, "Tidelands Oil Bill," 3/27/50; #965
  Senate, radio, "Small Business," 4/5/50; #929
  Senate, radio, "Small Business," 4/10/50; #854
  Senate, radio, "Economy in Government," 4/19/50; #657
  Senate, radio, "Substitute Displaced Persons Act," 5/15/50; #961
  Senate, radio, "ECA," 5/17/50; #923
  Senate, radio, "Control over Prices, Wages, and Materials; Defense Production," 6/27/50; #912
  Senate, radio, "Government Reorganization," 2/25/51; #927
  Senate, radio, "Government Reorganization; Letters from Constituents," 3/24/51; #930
  Senate, radio, "Women in Politics," 5/19/51; #960
  Senate, radio, "Aid to India," 6/11/51; #1043
  Senate, radio, "Defense Production Act; Emergency Economic Controls," 6/13/51; #1140
  Senate, radio, "Defense Production Act; Emergency Economic Controls," 7/9/51; #1139
  Senate, radio, "Emergency Economic Controls," 7/17/51; #1134
  Senate, radio, "Emergency Economic Controls," 7/11/51; #1141
  Senate, radio, "Letters from Constituents," 8/6/51; #931
  Senate, radio, "Government Reorganization," 9/3/51; #918
  Senate, radio, "Benton Amendment to Mutual Security Act and Monopolistic Nature of European Economy," 9/19/51; #1126
  Senate, radio, "Record of First Session of 82nd Congress," 10/22/51; #1130